[sweet airy music]
SEPTEMBER 08, 2011
50 DAYS OF DATING
[Ung] Every now and then,
Yeon-su would ask me really weird stuff.
You ever thought what'd happen…
Hmm?
Like, when I get into college,
but somehow you get left behind?
- I will get into college.
- No, at this rate, I sincerely doubt it.
Feels like that's
what you really want to happen.
Relax, that's not what I want.
It's just a random what-if question.
You'd take the exams again,
after I get in?
Ever thought of that?
[hums in thought]
First of all,
that's not even gonna happen.
But let's pretend like if it does,
then I'd just study
somewhere near your school.
Every day I'll do my studying next to you,
with my own lunch.
You really like me that much?
[cheeky awkward music]
Hey. I asked you a question.
Hey.
Just focus on sweeping, will you?
- We're here to work, stop slacking off.
- I asked you, if you like me that much?
[chuckles softly]
- What's the matter with you?
- Hey.
340 DAYS OF DATING
- What if what?
- [Yeon-su] I was just wondering, what if…
[Ung] Occasionally,
she'd ask out of nowhere.
What is it this time?
What if you secretly went on a date?
Don't be ridiculous.
Why in the world would I do that?
Okay, then what if I do it?
You're going on a date?
- [muffled cough]
- I'm not.
It's hypothetical.
It's just a what-if question.
Ji-ung's gonna spy on you to make sure.
He'll what? Yeah, right.
I think I'll stick to you all day
just to make sure you don't.
[chuckles]
Okay? I swear, I'm being serious.
[Ung] I know you finish class
at 5 p.m. today. I'll see you soon.
Even though we saw each other yesterday?
You know, I'm beginning to think
you really like me a lot.
[Ung] Whatever,
class is starting now. Bye.
- [call ending]
- Hello?
750 DAYS OF DATING
[coughing, groaning]
Looks like it's the end of the road.
I don't know what's gonna happen.
What if…
[coughing]
What if what? Your fever went down.
Stop exaggerating.
It's just a what-if question.
You're the one exaggerating.
What if I never get better and,
what if this is it for me?
What? All right,
stop being ridiculous already.
[Ung] I suspect that Yeon-su enjoys
watching me suffer in agony.
There. You're all better.
Get up and have some porridge.
[door closes]
[Yeon-su] I just…
It's just there was a specific answer
I wanted to hear from him.
1,565 DAYS OF DATING
To be honest, he was a strange boy.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
Are you all done? Do you wanna switch?
I was just wondering, what if…
- Again?
- Yeah, just a thought.
Enough with your what-ifs.
I seriously don't care.
What if I suddenly had to go abroad
as an exchange student?
Did you… why did you sign up for that?
I didn't. It's just a what-if question.
That would be horrible.
Those things never work.
In fact, all my friends
broke up after going abroad.
[Yeon-su] At least, I could feel that
he liked me a lot more than he let on.
What if I get a job somewhere
and they require me to move somewhere far?
Then I'll… I'll follow you
and find a job there.
Or at the very least I'll just follow you.
Why?
Why would you wanna be
by my side all the time?
[Yeon-su] Aren't you tired
of our long relationship?
Huh?
Do you like me that much or not?
[Yeon-su] How should I put it?
He never said the most important thing,
no matter how hard I tried.
- [grunts]
- Ow, hey, don't!
- Fine, be like that.
- You don't have to be so violent.
- Whatever. I'm going.
- Hey. Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, stop.
What are you so upset about? Hey.
- Hey, wait. Stop.
- Don't follow me.
- Hey, wait!
- [Ung] Why did she have to keep
asking me that every single time?
It's so weird.
[Yeon-su] Seriously, there's just no way
he can be that dense, right?
1,670 DAYS OF DATING
And then one night, finally, I asked him
that question for the last time…
It's so peaceful.
- I was wondering what if…
- [deep inhale]
I thought we already banned that question.
This'll be the last time.
I promise you. Just one more.
I have no idea
why you keep doing this to me.
What if someday we eventually break up?
- Not gonna happen.
- It's still possible, though.
Not for me, it isn't.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
I mean I could maybe leave you someday.
Like, what if I abandon you?
[sighs]
It's just a what-if question.
I'm not saying it's gonna happen.
Just wondering what you'd do.
- I won't see you.
- [Yeon-su] Huh?
- Ever again.
- Hey, easy. That's pretty heartless.
- You'll never see me again, as in forever?
- Hmm.
What if I find you again myself?
I'll spray water, throw salt,
and then kick you out.
Doesn't have to be that harsh.
I'm not a demon, you know?
It'll be fine…
just don't leave me.
[Yeon-su] That was the first time
he ever looked at me that way.
[Ung] Looking back, I guess maybe…
that wasn't really
a what-if question for her.
You…
[spraying]
[soft pensive music]
[deep sigh]
[sighs]
And what about the salt?
[Ung] Seeing her here
right now in front of me…
[Yeon-su] … just blows my mind.
How did we ever cross paths again?
EPISODE 2
1792 DAYS OF SUMMER
- Hello, welcome sir.
- Hello. It's just the two of us today.
I see. Of course. A table for two.
- Hello.
- It may seem like a hassle,
but I always stand outside to welcome
our customers and usher them inside.
Many of them are regulars here.
They're almost…
they're pretty much family…
Hello, welcome, sir.
Please, if you can just go inside.
Hey, what's all this?
We're filming right now.
It's okay, just act natural
and pretend no one's looking at you.
Don't look at the camera.
- Am I being filmed as well?
- Just act normal.
Please, go inside now. Go on, sir.
Right there. Yeah, go on.
Keep going and stop looking at the camera.
You're staring at it, stop.
[Ji-ung] I guess you must be
a regular here at the restaurant?
- Ji-ung, what the hell is this?
- Cut!
Chang-sik, please. Give me a break.
I'll explain it to you. Just think of him
as some kind of producer.
Act natural and answer all his questions.
Don't be weird.
Pretend you don't know him.
Stop calling him by his name.
[Chang-sik] Oh, I get it.
- I'll just… I'll watch you do your thing.
- Okay.
- Do what you need to do, don't worry.
- Good.
- I'm cool.
- All right.
- Fascinating.
- And action.
- Oh, sorry! Someone man the counter!
- Excuse me.
- Oh, what a hectic day.
- [Yeon-ok] Coming!
Hey, Ji-ung, where is Ung right now?
I could really use him around here.
I told him to wake up early
and get here as soon as possible
to help out at the cash register.
That brat.
I think that
he has trouble sleeping these days.
Why? Has he been sick?
He's still struggling?
How long has it been?
- I thought he's better already.
- Mm-mm.
What's been stressing him out?
Is he eating right?
Is he pulling all-nighters
because of his drawings?
[Ho groans]
That boy! He never goes outside.
Being indoors all the time
isn't good for your mental health.
- Hey, Ji-ung, listen to me, you should--
- No, hold it. Wait.
I'll do it.
I should buy some tonic for my boy.
Honey, listen,
call Yong-tae and ask him to help us.
He can concoct a tonic.
- Okay.
- [Chang-sik] My goodness, you two.
He's not a little boy anymore.
He's a grown man
who can take care of himself.
- He'll figure it out, you're overreacting.
- Shut up.
Ji-ung, what's Ung up to?
Tell me, what do you think
he's doing right now?
Actually, I think he must have
just fallen asleep by now.
I'll visit him after filming later,
then I'll tell you.
Oh, thank you so much.
Yeah, do that. That'd be great.
Yeah. Thanks, Ji-ung.
- Okay, come here for a sec.
- Mm-hmm.
Take care of everything here later
so that I can visit Yong-tae
and ask him for the best tonic
he can come up with for Ung.
And then we can visit…
[deep breath]
- How have you--
- How have you?
I'm sure you didn't come here
to ask me how I've been doing.
[Yeon-su clears throat]
- You look--
- You look
like you're about to tell me that
I look good, which would be a big mistake.
[tense music]
[sighs]
Seeing as you're not getting upset,
I guess this visit's gotta be
something really important.
[Yeon-su] Amazing. How'd he manage
to become even more of an ass?
You see…
Hold on.
Are you… are you getting married?
No way.
Okay. Fine then. Just keep on talking.
[Yeon-su] Although, he seems
to have changed a lot too.
That's you, isn't it?
- No, it's not.
- You didn't even look at it.
I can immediately tell you're lying.
You're Go-oh, just admit it.
- I said I'm not.
- To be honest with you,
I didn't believe it at first.
'Cause there's no way you ever
working this hard in your life.
But the places you chose to draw
I thought they looked way too familiar.
You don't go out much. Easy giveaway.
- They look nothing special if you ask me.
- Plus, you had that interview.
I remember that you once told me
that you don't ever draw people.
It's pretty common for artists
not to draw any people.
Fine. Let's say
these were just suspicions.
This, however…
is proof.
NJ's manager posted this
on his social media recently.
You see that blurry guy
sitting in the back?
That's you
no matter how many times I look at it.
You recognized me?
Go-oh had a reputation
for being secretive.
He never showed up to his exhibitions
or even when he sold his paintings.
But he met NJ in person.
- I'm her fan.
- Hm. Okay. Sure, you are.
Anyway, I'm here to see Go-oh,
not Choi Ung.
Strictly business. I have a proposal.
Really?
Hmm.
Make your pitch.
[Yeon-su] I guess
everyone does change with success.
Look how cocky he is right now.
[cheeky music]
Thank you for considering.
Sir, our proposal is,
we would like to do a collaboration
between Soen Shop and your work.
It's a premium lifestyle select shop,
which would gel with your style.
We were thinking as a surprise
you could do a live drawing session,
as sort of a highlight event
during the opening day.
Would you be amenable to this arrangement?
No, thank you.
- Sorry?
- I said no.
May I ask if there's a specific reason?
I just don't want to.
But still,
if you give us a reason
for your reluctance,
then we can adjust our proposal for you.
No. There's no need for any of that.
It's okay. Thanks.
- Hey.
- Sorry, to whom are you speaking?
The artist Go-oh or Ung?
Are you gonna keep being childish
and get personal--
How could you say that, of course I'm not.
That's why I'm hearing you out right now.
Then why don't you like it?
Is it because of me?
It's a perfectly good proposal.
'Cause, I don't like
being in front of people.
Which you'd know
if you did your research. By the way…
Yeah, I guess it's also 'cause of you.
[deep sigh]
I see you've grown quite a bit.
I don't know.
[inhales]
As far as I can remember,
I've always been a lot taller than you.
Can you please just stop
being so immature about this?
Anyway, if you could please
take a look at this.
- And if you change your mind--
- [Ung] Whom are you talking to again?
- Go-oh? Or Ung?
- Hey.
[Yeon-su] I swear
I should have never visited him.
All he did was humiliate me.
- What are you doing here, Yeon-su?
- What?
I told you to stay away from me forever.
I'm here
in a strictly professional manner.
So just for work? That's all it is?
Getting this proposal
is very important to me.
I don't know.
Doesn't seem important enough
to come find me after five years.
How are you still so upset
even after five years have passed?
How are you so indifferent
only after five years?
[soft gentle music]
What are you doing?
Am I dreaming?
'Cause unless I am, that woman
looks eerily similar to Yeon-su.
Nice to see he hasn't changed either.
What the?
She even sounds exactly like her.
Wow, this is so trippy.
I can't believe I'm dreaming of you
meeting your ex-girlfriend again.
I think we're done here now,
you should go home.
Despicable jerk.
What the hell?
What's going on? Is this for real?
Holy shit, what is Yeon-su doing in here?
[doorbell ringing]
Come on. Get the door.
Oh, okay.
[awkward music]
Who is it?
All right, I'm definitely still asleep.
This is way too messed up to be real.
- It's gotta be a dream.
- What the hell's wrong?
This has to be a dream.
- Oh?
- Good morning, it's nice to see you.
It's okay. That's actually normal for me.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yeah, it has, but you didn't even call.
You rarely pick up at this hour,
so I thought I'd just visit.
- [NJ] Can I come in, please?
- Sure.
[chuckles]
So who are all these people in your house?
- Are these your employees?
- Yeah.
I'm going now.
[door opens]
Jerk thinks he can look down on me
just 'cause he's all successful now.
Since when did he become
all high and mighty?
Whoa.
[cheeky music]
[gasps]
Good riddance.
[cheeky music]
[sighs]
[Ung] Well, that was satisfying.
That's one thing off my bucket list.
[scoffs]
How dare you show up here?
What are you doing, man?
Don't keep her waiting. Go talk to her.
It looks like you had
a guest over just now.
Oh, yeah.
I wasn't expecting you to visit today.
Actually, I was a bit thoughtless.
I'm used to being welcomed
even when I'm not expected, sorry.
Don't be sorry. It's all good, I swear.
Hello. My name is Gu Eun-ho.
I'm Ung's manager and his friend.
Uh, you can ask me
if you want to purchase his work,
visit his upcoming exhibitions.
Anything related to him, you can ask me.
I'm the man you need.
So it's Ung?
I guess that's your real name?
Yeah. It's Choi Ung.
Oh.
I have to apologize,
did I come over too early today?
No, not at all.
Feel free to come whenever you want.
We're very accommodating to visitors.
The studio's always open.
All year round, 24-7.
Why would my studio--
If you have any questions,
you can barge in whenever you wish.
We'll unlock the door for you,
even at night.
We're honored someone as shabby
as you came to this precious…
No, you're precious. Someone as precious
as you came to this shabby place…
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry about it.
People often stutter when they talk to me.
[NJ] I'm used to it. It's nothing new.
Can I have a tour of your studio?
- [sharp inhale]
- Of course, you can. Right?
It's okay, right?
Of course it's fine.
Right this way, if you please.
[cheery music]
[Ung] I'm never gonna forget this day.
Truly a gratifying moment.
[NJ] Are you okay there?
Oh, yeah.
- [exaggerated] Thank you for the food.
- No, thank you for eating here.
- Go.
- [loudly] Your food is always delicious.
Oh, my goodness, you're way too kind, sir.
[yelling]
I hope you succeed.
Thank you.
You've been wonderful. Have a great day.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Goodbye.
[Ho] Just keep walking, sir. Keep walking.
I was wondering, how come
you gave me a free fried egg today?
- You don't usually do that.
- [Ho] Thanks!
- [gentle music]
- [Ho] Just leave. Go.
Okay, my name is Ju Chang-sik
- and I own Seoul Hardware--
- Yeon-su?
You never even gave me a warning.
How dare you let me look this ugly
in front of her?
You did it on purpose. You traitor.
[Ung] I know I'm right.
This is a gratifying moment.
- [sighs]
- [NJ] So I was thinking…
I had been waiting for this day.
[NJ] Excuse me?
[groaning in pain]
She's calling you, you idiot.
Can you draw something for me?
Uh, you mean…
There's something specific
I'd like you to draw.
Uh, I see.
Except, I don't normally draw people.
I usually draw backgrounds
such as buildings or nature, like trees.
It's a building, don't worry too much.
My building.
- Sorry?
- I'd like you to draw the buildings I own.
- Make them pretty.
- Wow. She's incredible.
These days, I find it difficult
to derive joy from my life.
Simply put, I'm always bored,
no matter what I do.
[NJ] When it comes down to it,
this isn't the reason
- I worked so hard throughout my life.
- Oh, dear.
But then when I look at my buildings,
there's this indescribable feeling
that hits me.
I guess you could say it feels refreshing.
I feel more alive, I have an appetite,
and actually sleep well at night.
Looking at them gives me
a sense of reassurance.
I'm glad.
It's the same feeling I get
when I look at your work.
Oh, thanks.
[NJ] Looking at them,
I find peace and balance.
Buildings they're the only things
in this world that remain the same.
Do you also own any buildings?
No, of course not. He's paying month--
[groans]
So what do you say?
Are you willing to draw one up for me?
Think about it it'll benefit you
if they find out
I bought another piece of yours.
Uh, wait a sec. You think it'll be okay?
[Ung] I mean, you're an idol, so…
it could change your reputation a bit
if people find out
that you purchased buildings.
[NJ] I don't care about that.
Maintaining this pristine,
but manufactured image people had of me
never brought me any joy in my life.
If I'm gonna be happy, better start now.
I'll do what I want from now on.
Oh.
Let me have a moment to think about it.
[groans]
It's cool. I'm sure he can do it.
Oh, and I was wondering,
didn't you say earlier
that you were my fan?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
Well, it doesn't seem like you are.
It's almost like
you're sick of me already.
I'm not sure what you mean?
[chuckles]
It just seems like
you're a bit distracted today.
I don't know what it is.
I've got a knack
for noticing things like this easily.
Oh, I don't think that's why I seem--
It looks like I should get going now.
See you next time.
Oh. Wait, let me walk you to the door.
[gentle pensive music]
[Ung] It's not fair.
Why does it keep bothering me?
[Yeon-su] Childish little prick.
I don't need him to do me this favor.
I still have my pride too.
I'm never gonna let him
humiliate me again.
I seriously hope you weren't bluffing
about getting the artist
to work on this project.
You can't possibly
be that pathetic, can you?
[groaning sigh]
Oh, I shouldn't have overreacted.
Should I let myself go
and beg him just this once?
There's no way.
The guy literally threw salt at me.
[scooter honking]
[gasps]
What are you daydreaming
in the middle of the road for?
Hey.
It's a narrow alley.
You should be more careful.
It's been ages, you know that right?
What brings you all the way out here?
I should be asking you the same thing.
What are you doing all the way out here?
Oh, right. I guess you live here as well.
Don't tell me you're here to see Choi Ung.
Don't even get me started.
I came to see the great Go-oh,
- but instead I got treated like a doormat.
- What do you mean?
Is that guy ever gonna actually grow up?
He's become even more immature.
Let me guess,
did he spray water and throw salt at you?
How'd you know he'd do that?
Because he practiced doing that
on Eun-ho more than 50 times.
What?
Let's just say
he's a lot crazier than you thought.
[sighing]
Funny. I had no idea
that you'd actually see him again.
I guess all that practice really paid off.
I'm getting dizzy.
I can't believe I thought I could
just talk to him. I must be crazy.
- What have I been thinking?
- Why, what's wrong?
It's just, I had to see him
regarding this work proposal.
Forget it.
Not like I'm getting anywhere
with that lost cause.
See you around.
Oh.
Oh, my God, I'm such a ditz.
We haven't seen each other
in ages, have we?
How have you been doing, Kim Ji-ung?
[soft music]
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
Was I too harsh with the salt?
[sighs]
[soft music]
[Yeon-su] Grandma, wake up, let's eat.
[Ja-gyeong groans]
Oh, that was quick.
Is it already dinner time?
- Uh-huh, eat up and go to bed.
- [groans]
What time is it?
Oh, I need to stay up for the drama,
I don't wanna miss it.
They're not on yet. You have time to eat.
[Ja-gyeong] How could someone
be so beautiful and have glowing skin?
Oh, come on, grandma,
I just washed my face. That's all.
Lately I've been seeing her
on TV more often.
How could her face be so tiny?
It's like she was blessed
by the angels themselves.
Grandma, who do you think's prettier?
Her or me?
- What are you going on about?
- Huh?
You're really starting
to hurt my feelings over here.
I'm your actual granddaughter,
she's a stranger on TV.
And most likely she has a grandma too.
What? What kind
of ridiculous answer is that?
Did you even hear me?
The perfect answer
to your absurd question, that's what.
[Ja-gyeong] Now eat up
before the food gets cold.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe
I have your exact personality.
That's why
I'm so hot-tempered around everyone.
Good. Being hot-tempered
is a must if you're poor.
Don't let others look down on you. Okay?
I guess I've been
a little too kind these days, haven't I?
Maybe that's why I've been feeling like
I've been dragged
- around lately.
- You what? Who's been treating you wrong?
Who was it? Who made
my granddaughter feel all down and sad?
- [Ja-gyeong] Take me to that scumbag.
- [chuckles]
You bring all those bastards
to me right now.
I'm gonna teach those brats
a lesson they'll never forget.
- When I'm through with them--
- You're definitely my grandma.
[laughs]
You just grab this black part…
- Okay.
- …and push it in. It's very simple, right?
- All right, I got it. Yeah.
- Now go bring it outside.
All right. Yup.
- [distant bar music]
- [sniffs]
[Eun-ho] Excuse me, sir.
- Two dark beers for table five, please.
- Sure. Hold on, wait.
Once you're done with that,
just go home. You're all done here now.
Why do you keep coming here
and helping us out?
You're making me feel guilty.
You've been giving me an allowance.
I should do something in return.
And I'm saying you don't have to.
[man] Excuse me, sir,
two more beers over here, please.
Oh, sure.
- [Sol-i] Excuse me.
- Yes, just one minute.
Here are your dark beers.
Two of them. Enjoy your dinner.
Yes, what would you like, ma'am?
- One half-and-half spicy chicken.
- Okay.
And then one chicken salad.
Mm…
One tteokbokki, chicken feet fried rice.
- And this one as well.
- Okay, sure.
Sorry, are you gonna drink those?
Yeah, I will.
[Eun-ho] I'll go and get your order ready.
[camera clicking]
Your food is here, ma'am.
Thank you for waiting.
Tteokbokki and chicken feet friend rice.
You sure you can finish all that?
Sorry? Why would you even ask me that?
Of course I can, don't worry.
I'll finish all of it.
Hmm. Here's why.
- This one is on the house, ma'am.
- [gasps]
These are our crispy tenders.
It's our brand new dish, and it's
the most popular one this month, so enjoy.
Really? Are you sure
- you're giving this for free?
- Of course.
Seeing how much you've ordered,
I can tell these dishes are really good.
Do you have a mukbang channel?
Oh, I think I've seen you
in an online video before.
[gasps]
No, you're mistaken. But thanks anyway.
- Opened a business nearby?
- Yes. What?
It's okay.
It's not a bad thing to size
your rivals up. It's pretty normal.
If you look around,
many of our customers are just like you.
I saw you writing down
something on a notepad.
What did you write?
[clears throat]
Where's your business located?
What's it called? A restaurant? A bar?
I said that you're mistaken.
I don't know
why you're asking me all this.
Why do you have to make me
uncomfortable about ordering so much food?
You see, I'm extremely close
with the owner of this place.
- I can ask him the recipes for you.
- Oh, my God, can you really…
No, why would I want that?
You're wrong about me. What time is it?
I should get going, it's getting late.
- I'd like to pay the bill.
- What about all this food?
You're not eating? If you want
I can pack them to-go for you.
Yes. You can do that.
I'm glad.
I hope you savor the food slowly and
eventually find out what the recipes are.
Good luck.
[sighs]
- Thank you.
"Super tasty, extremely tasty,
incredibly tasty."
Her business is gonna go under.
[crickets creaking]
[sharp inhale]
Hey.
Why are you sleeping so pitifully?
You're already pitiful, to begin with.
[groans]
I couldn't sleep well this morning.
I heard Yeon-su came by.
Get that away. It's blinding me.
- How did you know?
- I ran into her earlier.
Was it before or after we met?
After you threw salt at her.
[sighs]
Did she tell you that?
No, she didn't have to.
I know you've been
rehearsing that for years.
Have you gone insane?
You're the one who was acting weird and
yet I'm the one who's feeling embarrassed.
[sighs]
I had no idea I'd see her again.
What's it like seeing her again?
Don't know.
Don't even remember what I said.
Well, I bet you said
all sorts of outrageous things.
Hey. Did you come over here
to pick a fight?
What? What're you so curious about?
Well, let's see…
Just wondering what your mental age is.
Oh, stop that.
Hey. By the way,
was there anything else she say?
About anything.
- Hm?
- Not much.
[sighs]
I see.
[soft music]
Let's go inside. It's chilly.
Actually, I'm going home.
What? What did you come over here for?
- Beats me.
- [scoffs]
Bye.
[Ung groans]
[soft music continues]
[crickets creaking]
[Ji-ung] Beats me.
[music fades]
[Yeon-su] Hey, grandma, I'm heading out.
Remember what I told you.
If anyone looks down on you…
[grunts]
Don't you worry,
I'm never gonna forget that.
[Yeon-su] She made everything simpler.
Everything's clearer now.
I should tell them the truth
and not be dispirited.
- Hello, how you doing?
- Then fix the issue.
Ms. Kook, you're looking like
you're in a very good mood today.
[chuckles]
Is that so?
[Yeon-su] I'll tell him
that I can't get Go-oh,
and then I'm gonna propose
an outstanding alternative.
I'll show him
what I've got and impress him.
He won't know what hit him
when I'm through.
[I-hun] Oh, and Mr. Bang is just with--
Hey, Ms. Kook, you're here.
[door closes]
Oh, Mr. Jang Do-yul paid us a visit
early in the morning today.
I heard the project is going well.
We were discussing it.
[nervous chuckle]
[Yeon-su] So much
for showing him what I've got.
Seems like you clock in
very late in the day, Ms. Kook.
[chuckles]
No, that's not it.
All of this is on purpose.
For a more creative vibe,
our workers clock in whenever they want.
It gives them more productive freedom.
After all, creativity stems
from a great work environment.
Sorry, I wasn't prepared.
I didn't expect to see you here
so early in the morning.
We have numerous
important matters to discuss,
and I'd like to attend
Soen Shop's soft launch together.
To gain perspective on our approach.
All right.
Come with me, sir. I'll fill you in.
I think I'll go with Ms. Kook.
After all, isn't she the one
overseeing this entire project?
Exactly, I agree. Going there
with a hands-on staff would be
the most efficient way of doing things.
What are you still doing there?
- Hurry up and go with him already.
- Yes, um…
[Yeon-su] Fantastic,
something I'm not prepared for.
Uh, Mr. Jang, sir?
I was wondering,
did you get home safe that night?
By any chance…
do you not remember what happened?
Sorry?
[elevator chiming]
[bell ringing]
[salsa music]
Ms. Kook, wait.
I think you're a little too drunk,
so slow down and--
I told you. I don't get drunk easily.
Why would you even think
I'd be that way after I…
I'd appreciate it if you walked
in a straight line for a minute.
Why aren't you using your umbrella?
Can't you see it's pouring out here?
Umbrella?
I…
[mumbling]
I don't…
I don't have an umbrella.
[crying]
Unfortunately, I don't have one!
[sobbing]
I don't have an umbrella…
Oh, my God, my umbrella…
[Yeon-su] What… what is this flashback?
Why am I remembering this?
[elevator chiming]
[Do-yul] Are you getting out?
Yes. I am, thanks.
Let's use my car.
Okay.
[car beeping]
[door closes]
- [whooshing]
- [engine rumbling]
Excuse me, Mr. Jang.
Yes, Ms. Kook, what is it?
You won't believe what's happening.
Someone is stealing your car
right now. Call the cops.
He's not stealing it.
He's actually driving the car for me.
Don't worry about a thing, Mr. Jang.
I'll keep a close eye on him,
so he won't get away.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Is she… is she gonna be okay?
Excuse me!
[shushing]
You need to watch it.
Mr. Jang has a nasty temper.
He's not gonna show any mercy.
Now I think
you're just deliberately bashing me.
[quirky music]
You're awfully quiet today, Ms. Kook.
- Sorry?
- What's the matter? Remembering something?
Not at all. I'm afraid I have no idea
what you're talking about. Nope.
- I think you know what it is.
- [scoffs]
No, I don't understand. What you mean?
How much do you remember from that night?
Do you remember mumbling
and ranting about anything at all?
Or calling me a sociopath?
- [distant police sirens]
- What?
[quirky music]
[mumbling]
You think you're a sociopath.
Sorry?
You're a frigid, cold-hearted man
who will walk all over anyone
in his way to achieve success.
You sure you're talking about me?
"I may not be able
to empathize with others,
but I'm a cold-hearted man
who's intelligent and good at his job."
Ms. Kook. I don't think--
Unbelievable.
TVs really can throw you off.
They have a distorted image of people
instead of the truth.
My grandma and I watch this drama,
there's this character
who's exactly like you.
People think they're cool,
but in reality,
they're all a bunch of losers.
- Fake ass bastards.
- [snickers]
Ms. Kook, please.
Don't say anything you'll regret--
No! I wasn't finished!
Stop cutting me off. Will you?
Why do you keep cutting me off?
It's really very rude of you.
How would you like it
if I cut your neck off?
[awkward music]
[Yeon-su] Mr. Jang, I'm sorry.
I sincerely apologize
for everything I said that night.
I'm truly sorry.
So you remember
everything up to that point.
I am extremely sorry.
I am… I don't have any excuses.
I was drunk and I made a huge--
I thought you never got drunk.
That was an incredible display.
Okay. Is there anything
that I can I do for you to forgive me?
No, it's fine. Please just make sure
this upcoming project goes smoothly.
- Well, you see, that's…
- We're here now.
[soft sigh]
Ung. Hey!
- Ung.
- You startled me.
- I just fell asleep. What is it?
- What's this, huh?
What about it?
What is this? I saw it on the table.
Who gave this to you?
Oh, that? Yeon-su gave it to me.
Yeon-su did? No way.
You're telling me this is what she does?
More importantly,
is this the reason she came to see you?
Unbelievable.
Oh, so that's why
she went all the way here.
Makes sense. It's not like
she would've stooped so low
just to come back to see you, would she?
- Right?
- What are you talking about?
- You take her up on it?
- I didn't. I refused.
Are you crazy? Why would you do that?
Did you even read any of it?
No. Why should I?
I don't wanna do it.
She talked about doing
some live show or something
so I flatly rejected her right away.
You know I don't do those kinds of things.
But, you'll be, you'll be drawing
Soen Shop. It's Soen Shop.
So? What is that?
[sighs]
It's a new shop that has launched
in Paris, London, and now over here.
Are you nuts?
You should've said yes immediately.
This is a great opportunity.
You of all people should be doing this.
Why should I?
[Eun-ho] Because Jean Ferrat
designed the damn building. Look.
[gasps]
How did you not know
your favorite architect was involved?
Get off your ass.
Go to Yeon-su this instant and tell her
that, "Fine, you're gonna do it."
Why did you have to act all tough
and throw salt at her?
You're an idiot. You messed up.
Now go over there and beg for it.
WORLD-FAMOUS ARCHITECT, JEAN FERRAT
[sighs]
Damn it. I won't do it.
[groans]
Now I know you're crazy.
You're really opting out of this?
Okay. Wait there.
Let me show you the Soen Shop.
SOEN SHOP
Oh? They're having a soft launch today.
Today?
Let's go. Just go take a look, Ung,
I bet it will change your mind.
[staff 1] NJ. One hour before rehearsals.
Please ready everything.
[Chi-seong] Okay, will do.
Hey, everyone, let's get ready, come on!
Why hasn't he called me?
[Mi-yeon] Who?
You know, that artist.
- [Mi-yeon] Did he say that he'd call you?
- Yeah. I asked him to do me a favor.
He said he'd think about it
and give me a call.
[Mi-yeon] How long has it been?
- About a day and three hours?
- [chuckles]
[Mi-yeon] Come on.
And here I thought it was a big deal.
To you, it's not, but to me, it is.
He's an artist.
And a pretty famous one at that.
These people,
they have a certain way of thinking.
He probably thinks you're a snob,
so he's cautiously taking his time.
No, that can't be the reason why.
Wait, is he handsome?
Not really. Actually…
[chuckles]
He kinda looks like an idiot.
- Well, well, well, exactly your type.
- [chuckles]
Exactly, I know.
Here's someone who's exactly my type,
and he's not even messaging me.
Chi-seong. Is my schedule today--
[Chi-seong] No, it's full.
It's completely packed.
- Can I skip any one of them?
- [Chi-seong] No, you can't.
See, what's happening is you're making up
for what you skipped the past two weeks,
so that's definitely not an option.
NJ. I can see that
you're racking your brain again
over something unimportant.
Can you please not do that, for now, hm?
- For my sake.
- Do you think I should call him first?
- [sighs]
- No, I can't.
Even if he's ordinary,
I've reached out to him too often already.
Actually, since he's an artist,
I guess he's kind of a celebrity too.
So it's no big deal if I call him first.
[distant phone ringing]
[sighs]
Are you going to do it?
- No, I'm not. Why?
- Then why keep watching?
- Because…
- If you ask me, it looks kinda fun.
Why?
Look at them.
They're so lively, flopping around.
What are they like fish or something?
I like their chemistry
and distinct characters.
[Chae-ran] It's perfect
for the early summertime.
They're awkward, young and full of energy.
It's a youth documentary
that's more exciting than most dramas.
I guess it's childish, but it also
talks about the issues
kids their age worry about, so,
I could understand
why the viewers loved it
and why they would wanna
see them again after some time.
All they did was
argue and fight the whole time?
Did you also watch the original?
Take a look when you have time,
you might change your mind.
The original?
When were you even able to watch that?
You were also in it.
I remember seeing you a lot.
- You were rather cute when you were 19.
- Yeah, whatever.
Anyway, take a look at it.
No, thanks. Don't have any time for that.
I'm heading off to shoot some footage.
[Ji-ung] Bye.
[sighs]
EDITING ROOM
[groans]
[sighs]
Why the hell am I doing this?
SBC SPECIAL
[wheels rattling]
[mouse clicking]
[gentle music]
Once we remove the barricades
on the opening day,
there won't be enough room.
You should consider that too.
- [Yeon-su] Okay.
- Hello. Over here this way. I'll show you.
Since the showroom is on the third floor,
the guest should
take a tour through here first.
I'll send you an email about it later.
Should I put these items
where they can be more visible?
So the guests can see them?
Mr. Jang?
Okay.
They're nice.
[Eun-ho] What now?
You still don't wanna do it?
Go inside and you'll change your mind,
I'm telling you.
[bright music]
- [staff 2] Oh. I'm sorry sir.
- Yes?
The technicians are taking turns
inspecting the elevators.
- It'll take about 15 minutes more.
- No, that's fine.
We'll just take the escalator.
Let's go.
Our key features in the store
are furniture and lighting,
put them at the top
of the product placement list
when you create the plan.
Also, please make sure that we'll utilize
all the areas within the shop
as much as possible for publicity.
And please make a list of products
we can place in media,
that can be shown in dramas,
variety shows, or documentaries.
[Yeon-su] Yes, sir, will do.
[Do-yul] Oh and by the way,
- about that collaboration--
- Yo, Yeon-su! What's up?
[awkward music]
Okay, we'll go up there to you.
Just stay there. Wait for us.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, it's fine.
Do you need some privacy?
Oh, no, you can continue, please.
[Eun-ho] I think she's over there.
- Oh! Yeon-su!
- [Ung] What are you doing?
There you are.
- Hands off.
- I dragged him all the way here.
[Eun-ho] Aren't you glad?
Yeah, now please
drag him out of here, right now.
FYI, I didn't wanna come here.
I heard you wanted to work with him,
so I thought we'd meet up and hash--
You might as well tell everyone.
[awkward music]
[awkward chuckle]
Eun-ho, I'm in the middle
of work right now.
It's okay, Ms. Kook, I can give you
some privacy I'll just wait down--
Oh, no, that's okay. Just stay.
Excuse me, but are you like a friend
of Yeon-su or are you working with her?
Actually, he's the marketing team leader
of the Soen Shop company.
[Eun-ho gasps]
No way.
What a coincidence, 'cause we're
very interested in this place.
Ung, heard that?
He's the marketing team leader.
Stop embarrassing me.
Let's get out of here.
This is only our soft launch,
as you can see it's still hectic
around the whole building.
But I hope you enjoy it anyway.
Oh, if you're unsatisfied
or if you have any suggestions for us,
please feel free to tell our workers
on your way out.
Yeah, sure. Definitely.
Wow. You're very friendly.
I'm never gonna forget you.
Yeon-su, don't forget
to call me when you're done,
and we'll talk about the deal.
My number is…
Never mind. Just call Ung directly.
- Come on.
- Make sure you call him when you're free.
Don't forget to call us, okay, huh?
I'm so sorry about that, sir.
No, it's okay. They're interesting people.
What's the matter?
Uh, honestly I'm just a little surprised
that you weren't offended by--
Oh, because I didn't act
like a sociopath this time?
Oh, no. That's not why.
[nervous chuckle]
- Let's go.
- Okay.
[Eun-ho gasps]
[Eun-ho] Wow.
[Eun-ho] That team leader
has a handsome face.
How can a marketing guy
be so damn good-looking?
[sighs]
Seriously, if I didn't know who they were,
they look like a couple
when they're together.
[groans]
Hey. How could you talk about me
in front of everyone as my manager?
Oh, come on. Who do you think
you are? Batman or something?
Why are you so desperate to hide?
We didn't tell the whole world.
- Shut up.
- Hold up. You're leaving already?
You're not going
to talk to Yeon-su about the thing?
I'm going for a walk upstairs.
Look at you. You're totally
into this place, aren't you?
NJ, deep breath at the count of two.
One, two, now.
Done. Okay. Great.
- Okay.
- [gasps]
- Unzip me right now.
- What? Why?
- Hurry up. Do it.
- Hold on, all right.
There we go. Why? What's wrong?
MR. CHOI UNG
READ
Are you crazy?
How dare you ignore my text?
[Mi-yeon] The artist?
[chuckles]
Looks like you've met your match.
He's probably writing his reply.
He's just being
meticulous and prudent, right?
How long has it been?
Thirteen minutes?
I really don't get
young people like you these days.
[Mi-yeon] It's only been 13 short minutes.
You have the patience of a child.
Then again, he didn't strike me
as the prudent type.
Why does he keep ignoring me?
[soft chuckle]
Take it off, I'm not gonna use it.
- Chi-seong.
- [Chi-seong] Yes?
She's at it again. Please talk to her.
What? What is it this time? Tell me.
I can skip the rehearsal.
I don't need to do it.
I need to go out for a bit.
[button beeps]
Sir, I have to tell you something.
It's about the opening event plan.
- Go ahead, I'm listening.
- [soft chuckle]
You know that plan about the collaboration
with the artist I told you about?
Yes.
I don't think it'll pan out anymore.
Why not?
I wasn't able to contact him
no matter how hard I tried.
And through my extensive research on him,
we hit a roadblock. I found out that
he doesn't want to be seen in public.
- Ms. Kook, listen--
- I know you're disappointed about this.
However, I'm truly sorry.
In any case, I promise
that I'll come up with something else.
A better alternative.
I guess you really don't remember
what happened at the end.
What?
You remember up until
you called me a sociopath,
but it didn't end there.
You don't remember about
what happened in front of your house?
I don't get you.
[bright music]
[sighs]
I found out who Go-oh is.
[Yeon-su] Because I didn't want you
to look down on me.
That's actually really great news.
I really hoped it wasn't him.
I really didn't expect it to be him.
Sorry?
How do I do this…
How can I possibly see him again?
[Yeon-su hiccups]
I don't get what you mean.
[Yeon-su sniffling]
How am I gonna handle it?
[sniffs]
Seeing that jerk, Choi Ung,
after all this time?
You don't mean Go-oh, right?
You personally know him?
[Yeon-su] It's been five years
since we broke up.
Hey.
Hello, Ms. Kook?
Out of everyone in the world…
Why did it have to be Ung?
How am I supposed to face him?
[Yeon-su] What the? Son of a bitch!
What in the world did I tell him?
[inhales]
- That guy just now was Go-oh, wasn't he?
- You see--
[Do-yul] He seems to know
about this project.
Okay, if you're uncomfortable
about working with him on this,
we're willing to replace you with someone
who's more capable of handling it
and proceed with the original plan.
- But sir, it's--
- I'm saying, since you were in charge
from the get-go it'd be great
if you stayed on board to see it through.
However, we have no choice if you can't
put your personal feelings aside.
- [staff 3] Mr. Jang.
- Just one minute.
You're done for today, so you can leave.
Let me know if anything comes up.
You have my number. Goodbye.
- [Do-yul] Yes?
- [staff 3] Can you check this?
[Do-yul] Oh, that looks fine.
[sighs]
[Yeon-su] What should I do now?
Oh, no. What am I supposed to do?
Going in?
[sighs]
[button beeps]
[both sigh]
Where is Eun-ho?
Somewhere downstairs.
[rattling]
Whoa.
Right. They said they were
inspecting the elevators.
[sighs]
EMERGENCY CALL
We're stuck in elevator nine.
Please send assistance.
- It won't take long, don't worry.
- You don't look too surprised.
Is there a reason that I should be?
[clears throat]
Thought you said you weren't interested.
What changed?
I read the proposal today.
I knew it. You didn't even bother
reading it that day.
It blows my mind. How are you
still so immature after all these years?
With the water and the salt,
I heard you rehearsed that several times.
- Did Ji-ung tell you that?
- Just grow up, will you?
Seriously, that's all you could think of?
What about you?
Was that the only excuse
you could think of after five years?
Then what excuse were you expecting
to hear when you saw me outside your door?
[sentimental tense music]
[Yeon-su] One thing was for sure,
I wasn't gonna be childish like you.
After all, it had been five years already.
What if I had stopped behaving childishly?
Would you have stayed with me?
[sentimental music]
If you were being sincere back then,
tell me, what would you have done?
[sentimental music continues]
I'm sorry. They must have
made a mistake during the inspection.
No, it's okay. Thank you.
[sentimental music]
[Ung] I really am childish.
I just ran away.
[NJ] How's it going?
Oh.
NJ, hey, what are you doing here?
- Do you know where your phone is?
- Where my phone is?
It's right here in my pocket.
Oh, so you didn't lose it after all.
Then why have you been ignoring me?
Oh, that. I turned it off
because I wanted a bit more time to think
what I'd say to you,
you know, before replying.
[NJ] So you put off my text?
I'm curious,
what were you doing that time?
I was… I went out somewhere.
What about you?
What are you doing around here?
Do you have, like, an event here?
No reason. I was just wondering
why you were ignoring me.
But… aren't you really busy?
Don't you have a packed schedule?
I do, I'll be leaving in five minutes.
I have a live stage scheduled.
I just had a bit of free time to kill.
- So you came here?
- I'm usually too busy to feel bored,
fortunately, things have
changed a lot these days.
I wanted to see what you were so busy with
instead of replying to my text.
What?
Um, you know, you're very…
What should I say?
I'll just use the word unique.
I'm running late. You take care.
Hold on, is that why you came
all the way out here? To check up on me?
You wanna find out?
Easy, just ignore my text again.
[NJ] Let's go.
[chuckles]
[chuckling on screen]
SBC SPECIAL
HWIYEONG HIGH SCHOOL
[Ung on screen] Hey! Whoa!
[mouse clicking]
[laughter on screen]
[sighs]
[dial tone]
Hello.
Okay, I'll do it. I'm in.
["Drawer" by 10cm playing]
[exhales]
SBC SPECIAL
[Ung and Yeon-su laughing on screen]
What? What do you want me to do?
- What?
- You don't have a choice.
[groans]
Don't annoy me so early in the morning.
I need to do it, and that means so do you.
- Does my Dad wanna film me too?
- [Ji-ung] No, that's not it.
You and Yeon-su.
Just like before. A documentary.
["Why" by Janet Suhh playing]
Are you insane? What drugs are you on?
Think I'm some kind
of a doormat you can step on?
Hello everyone, I'm Choi Ung.
It's nice to meet you.
EPILOGUE
[deep inhale]
My name is…
[Yeon-su groans]
Are we seriously gonna do this again?
[sighs]
[whistles]
1792 DAYS OF SUMMER
[upbeat music]
[Ji-ung] Think about it, why would people
decide to star in a documentary?
There's a good reason.
My skin used to be so elastic.
[Ung sighs]
The things I hate?
Yeah, it's still Kook Yeon-su.
[Eun-ho] To put Ung and Yeon-su together
after what they've been through…
Wouldn't that be a little too disastrous?
Wait. Wait. My crutch!
Why would I?
You mean absolutely nothing to me. Zero.
I've never met anyone so selfish,
she's so full of herself.
[Yeon-su] All right,
let's see who wins this.
How precious it is to be able to capture
and store a moment in your life.
[Ji-ung] Just be honest with me.
Does none of that
really mean anything to you?